BRYAN BILLHIMER: In this next step, we're going to talk about pull-offs.
We're going to pluck the 17th fret and we're going to pull our finger off to the 15th fret.
So, this requires two fingers.
You're going to have your finger on the 17th fret and you got another finger on the 15th fret and you're going to pluck the 17th fret, you're going to pull that finger off to the 15th fret.
So, let's see what a pull off looks like on guitar.
So, our tab told us 17th fret on the B string, so I'm going to use my third finger.
I'm going to fret the 17th fret and I know that I'm going to be pulling off to the 15th fret so I'm going to go ahead and fret the 15th fret with my first finger.
So, it's going to look like that.
I'm going to pick and I'm going to pull off in kind of a down and up at the same time motion with my third finger, kinda down and up.
Then I'm going to pull off so we're going to hear the note that's being fret above the 15th fret.
And that's a pull off.
In a riff, it might be something like.... And that's a pull off.